

#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# **NGUYEN VAN MINH**

Software Engineer

# : 12 December, 1997

⊠: ngxvanminh@gmail.com

☎: 0908 120 803

## **EDUCATION**

08/2015 - 07/2019

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology and Education

Major: Electrical & Electronics Engineering

GPA: 7.4

### **CERTIFICATES**

Application of Revit MEP to setup shop drawing of M&E system

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm interested in develop system and always excited to learn new technology to apply in my project. My strengths are logical thinking, programming, teamwork skill and self study

In 5 years, I hope to advance in my role as much as possible. I enjoy to code and think it is the right choice for me long term. I want to continue working in a professional environment where every employee can improve

# **SUMMARY INFORMATION**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/minhngx

- Experience in programing C/C++ in embedded system
- Experience in programing SQL, Python about Data Science
- Strong technical in PLC programing
- Technical Skills:
  - Tools: AutoCAD, Proteus, LabVIEW
  - Languages: C/C++, Python, SQL, HTML/CSS
  - Framework: tensorflow, pandas, matplotlib, seaborn, sklearn, opencv, selenium
  - Microsoft Office: Excel, Power BI, Visio, SharePoint
  - Git (https://minhngx.github.io)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

| _                 |   |
|-------------------|---|
| 04/2021 – now     | Bosch Global Software Technologies Viet Nam Position: Embedded Software Engineer  |
|                   | <ul> <li>Tasks:</li> <li>Veryfying the automotive software configuration at Unit test for Active Safety (ABS, EPS) to coverage code</li> <li>Understanding code flow, writing script tests for every complex situation</li> <li>Reporting the real deviation and making a discussion with customers to deal with these issues</li> <li>Compiling documents to improve job productivity, also as training materials</li> <li>Knowledge of black-box and white-box testing</li> </ul>   |
| 12/2019 - 03/2021 | Intel Products Vietnam Position: Process & Equipment Engineer   |
|                   | <ul> <li>Tasks:</li> <li>Repairing and sustaining motherboard of chipsets, SOC and CPU, conducting follow-ups with technicians to ensure minimal issues for motherboard</li> <li>Using SQL, JMP and Python script to monitor and visualize the process to detect signals and maintain it within control</li> <li>Monitoring equipment and process indicators to reduce process variability</li> <li>Coordinating, implementing and developing equipment and process improvements in regards to safety, quality and efficiency by applying 8D, FMEA, MBPS, 5 whys</li> </ul> |

## **PROJECTS**

#### Product checking system by LabVIEW - HCMUTE

Final Thesis

⇔ https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nrMJN-T33D8

The project detects 3 common errors in industry. Error signals are connected to the web for easy observe and control

LabVIEW, Siemens, HTML/CSS, Modbus, Web server, Computer Vision

Face Recognition - Minh Nguyen

Project Owner

⇔ https://github.com/minhngx/face\_detection

The project simple face regognition tool, which combine Conputer Vision and Face Embedded

Python, SQL, numpy, OpenCV